■ Overview:
  ---------
This DMA Device driver is a software component that provides an interface over DMA. DMA in Tiva C can be used over
many peripherals. In thins driver it is used over UART.
DMA has many modes according to the type of the transmitter and receiver, In This driver it is implemented to 
work in the "memory to Peripheral" mode.


■  Technical features and user guide:
  -----------------------------------
■  Description
  -------------
DMA Driver Provides an interface over UART to get the data in packets specified by transfer size 
(The used packet is 1024 byte). 

■ The Driver provides 4 functions 
  --------------------------------
  DMA_Init(void): This function initializes DMA clock Gating control for DMA and set the initial configurations 
  specified in the configuration file. It also assigns the needed values in the required register to select
  a proper DMA channel.

  DMA_RetType DMA_StartChannel(uint8_t DMAGroupID,uint32_t SRC, uint32_t DES, uint16_t TransferSize): This 
  function initiates a transfer between a source and a destination with the required  transfer size (which can
  be between a number between 1 to 1024)

  DMA_RetType DMA_StopChannel(uint8_t ChannelID): This function disables the addresed channel 

  void DMA_Done(void): This function is excuted on interrupts in cas of SWTransfer requests.

■ steps
  -----
  1- Configure the required configurations in the config file. 
  2- initialize the DMA.
  3- Start the Transfer with the specified source & destination addresses
	* In case of peripheral address, An interrupt handler must be provided on the peripheral end that
		handles DMA completion interrupt.
        * In case of memory to memory you can use the callback function at the end of completion To indicate
	  the end of transfer.





